Guide to the Rural indexes and maps, 1920-1940, 1959
Rural indexes and maps, 1920-1940, 1959
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Rural indexes and maps, 1920-1940, 1959.
3953
Rural Directories, Inc.
1.5 cubic ft.
Maps, indexes, and directories.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
"Compass system" maps and rural indexes of New York State counties published by Rural Directories, Inc. Also, rural directories published by others.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
"Compass system" maps and rural indexes of New York State counties published by Rural Directories, Inc. Also, rural directories published by others.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Rural Directories, Inc.
Subjects:
Rural development--New York (State).
Places:
Albany County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Allegany County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Broome County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Cayuga County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Chemung County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Chenango County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Cortland County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Erie County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Fulton County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Genesee County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Herkimer County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Jefferson County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Livingston County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Madison County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Monroe County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Montgomery County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Niagara County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Oneida County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Onondaga County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Ontario County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Orleans County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Oswego County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Otsego County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Rensselaer County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Saratoga County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Schenectady County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Schuyler County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Seneca County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Steuben County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Tioga County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Tompkins County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Wayne County (N.Y.)--Directories.; Yates County (N.Y.)--Directories.
Form and Genre Terms:
Indexes.; Maps.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Albany County
  - Rural guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 1)
- Allegany County
  - Farm Plat Book and Directory, Allegany County Farm Locations. Allegany County Farm Bureau., 1959 (Box 1, Volume 1A)
- Broome County
  - "Clock system" rural index and map., 1922 (Box 2, Volume 2)
  - Rural Index, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Volume 3)
  - Rural Index and "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 4)
- Cayuga County
  - Rural Index., 1926-1927 (Box 1, Volume 5)
  - List of farms for merchants and manufacturers., 1928-1929 (Box 1, Volume 6)
  - Rural Index and "Compass system" map., 1936-1937 (Box 1, Volume 7)
- Chemung County
  - "Clock system" rural index and map., 1922 (Box 2, Volume 8)
  - Rural Index and "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 9)
  - Index (not. dupl. of no. 8)., 1922 (Box 2, Volume 54)
- Chenango County
  - "Clock system" rural index (with map)., 1927-1928 (Box 1, Volume 10)
  - List of farms for merchants and manufacturers., 1927-1928 (Box 1, Volume 11)
  - Rural guide (with map)., 1940 (Box 1, Volume 12)
- Cortland County
  - "Clock system" rural index and map., 1921 (Box 2, Volume 13)
  - Rural Index and "Compass system" map., 1937-1938 (Box 1, Volume 14)
  - Register of farms for merchants, manufacturers, and professional men., 1937-1938 (Box 1, Volume 15)
- Erie County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1940 (Box 1, Volume 16)
- Fulton and Montgomery Counties
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 17)
- Genesee County
  - Directory of farms for merchants, manufacturers, and professional men., 1929-1930 (Box 1, Volume 18)
  - Rural Index and Buying Guide (with 2 maps)., 1929-1930 (Box 1, Volume 19)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 20)
- Herkimer County (Southern section)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 21)
- Jefferson County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 22)
- Livingston County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 23)
- Madison County
  - "Clock system" rural index (with map) - of Cazenovia township only., 1920 (Box 1, Volume 24)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1937-1938 (Box 1, Volume 25)
- Monroe County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 26)
- Montgomery County - see Fulton County
- Niagara County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 27)
- Oneida County
  - List of farms and rural homes for merchants and manufacturers., 1928-1929 (Box 1, Volume 28)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 29)
- Onondaga County
  - List of all farms for merchants and manufacturers., 1928-1929 (Box 1, Volume 30)
  - Rural Index and Almanac with map., 1936 (Box 1, Volume 31)
  - Register of all farms for merchants, manufacturers, and professional men., 1936-1937 (Box 1, Volume 32)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 33)
- Ontario County
  - "Clock system" rural index., 1923 (Box 1, Volume 34)
  - Register of all farms for merchants, manufacturers, and professional men., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 35)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 36)
- Orleans County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 37)
- Oswego County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 38)
- Otsego County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1940 (Box 1, Volume 39)
- Rensselaer County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 40)
- Saratoga County - see Schenectady County
- Schenectady County (and Southern Saratoga County)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1939 (Box 1, Volume 41)
- Schuyler County - see also Seneca and Tompkins Counties
  - Rural Directory of all farms in Schuyler County., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 42)
- Seneca, Yates and Schuyler Counties
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 43)
- Seneca County
  - Rural Directory of all farms in Seneca County, 1938 (Box 1, Volume 44)
- Steuben County
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1940 (Box 1, Volume 45)
- Tioga County
  - "Clock system" Rural Index and map., 1922 (Box 2, Volume 46)
- Tompkins County
  - "Clock System" Rural Index Ithaca & Enfield Towns & map., 1920 (Box 1, Volume 57)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1937 (Box 1, Volume 47)
  - Register of farms for merchants (with map)., 1937-1938 (Box 1, Volume 48)
- Tompkins County (including Hector Township of Schuyler County)
  - "Clock system" Rural Index (with map)., 1925-1926 (Box 1, Volume 49)
  - "Compass system" map., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 55)
- Wayne County
  - "Clock system" Rural Index (with map)., 1922 (Box 2, Volume 50)
  - Rural Guide and "Compass system" map., 1937 (Box 1, Volume 51)
  - Register of farms for merchants, manufacturers, and professional men., 1937-1938 (Box 1, Volume 52)
- Yates County - see also Seneca County
  - Rural Directory (with map)., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 53)